these Stacks each represent sums of n
consecutive positive integers the first
one from 1 to n the second from 2 to n +
1 all the way up to the last one which
goes from n up to 2 N minus one when we
glue these Stacks together we get this
interesting shape here we can take a
second copy of this shape and rotate it
twice once the second copy is rotated
appropriately we see that the two copies
fit together perfectly to form a cuboid
with Dimensions n by n by 2 N that means
the number of cubes in the original
stack we started with is 12 * 2 n * n *
n this equals n cubed this means that
the sum of the consecutive sums of n
positive integers that we started with
equals n cubed so that we've uncovered
an interesting double sum formula for
cubic numbers